Guide to the Images of Yale Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Alphabetical List of Individuals, Series I
  - Rankin, Bernard Courtney (Box 56, Folder 2118)
  - Rankin, Hugh (Box 56, Folder 2118)
  - Ransom, Charles Newton (Box 56, Folder 2119)
  - Rathbone, Isaac T. (Box 56, Folder 2119)
  - Ratner, Arthur (Box 56, Folder 2119)
  - Rattle, William James (Box 56, Folder 2120)
  - Rawson, Edward Kirk (Box 56, Folder 2120)
  - Rawson, Frederick Holbrook (Box 56, Folder 2120)
  - Ray, Mrs. David H. (Box 56, Folder 2121)
  - Ray, Hurlon C. (Box 56, Folder 2121)
  - Raymond, B. P. (Box 56, Folder 2121)
  - Raymond, Daniel Leasure (Box 56, Folder 2121)
  - Raymond, Edward Artemas (Box 56, Folder 2122)
  - Raynes, Alphonse F., M.D. (Box 56, Folder 2122)
  - Reade, William Churchill (Box 56, Folder 2123)
  - Reagan, Ronald (Box 56, Folder 2124-25)
  - Reback, Judge Abraham (Box 56, Folder 2126)
  - Record, Samuel J. (Box 56, Folder 2126)
  - Reddington, Paul G. (Box 56, Folder 2126)
  - Redlich, Frederick C. (Box 56, Folder 2127)
  - Reed, Curtis Seaman (Box 56, Folder 2127)
  - Reed, Edward Bliss (Box 56, Folder 2127)
  - Reed, Frances C. (Box 56, Folder 2128)
  - Reed, Herbert Calhoun (Box 56, Folder 2128)
  - Reed, Harry Lothrop (Box 56, Folder 2128)
  - Reed, Ralph Duryea (Box 56, Folder 2129)
  - Reed, S. Leslie (Box 56, Folder 2129)
  - Reed, S. Luther (Box 56, Folder 2129)
  - Reed, Stanley Forman (Box 56, Folder 2130)
  - Reeve, Gen. Charles McC. (Box 56, Folder 2131)
  - Reeves, Jeremiah B. (Box 56, Folder 2132)
  - Regala, Judge Roberto (Box 56, Folder 2132)
  - Reich, Charlie (Box 56, Folder 2133)
  - Reichert, Frederick (Box 56, Folder 2134)
  - Reid, Edward W. (Box 56, Folder 2134)
  - Reifsnyder, W. E. (Box 56, Folder 2134)
  - Reily, George Wolf (Box 56, Folder 2135)
  - Reily, George Wolf, Jr. (Box 56, Folder 2135)
  - Reiner, Richard (Box 56, Folder 2135)
  - Relyea, Charles (Box 56, Folder 2136)
  - Remington, Fredric (Box 56, Folder 2137)
  - Renisin, Ira (Box 56, Folder 2138)
  - Rennell, H. H. (Box 56, Folder 2138)
  - Resnik, Dr. Edward (Box 56, Folder 2138)
  - Reynolds, Carlton M. (Box 56, Folder 2139)
  - Reynolds, Charles Olmsted (Box 56, Folder 2139)
  - Reynolds, E. S. (Box 56, Folder 2139)
  - Reynolds, E. V. (Box 56, Folder 2140)
  - Reynolds, H. S. (Box 56, Folder 2140)
  - Reynolds, Horatio McLeod (Box 56, Folder 2141)
  - Reynolds, James Bronson (Box 56, Folder 2142)
  - Reynolds, James William (Box 56, Folder 2142)
  - Reynolds, William Augustus, Jr. (Box 56, Folder 2143)
  - Reynolds, William Henry (Box 56, Folder 2143)
  - Reynolds, William [Saxby] (Box 56, Folder 2143)
  - Rhodes, Frank R. (Box 56, Folder 2144)
  - Rhodes, William Castle (Box 56, Folder 2144)
  - Rice, Abner (Box 56, Folder 2145)
  - Rice, Richard Austin (Box 56, Folder 2145)
  - Rice, William Henry (Box 56, Folder 2145)
  - Rich, Townsend (Box 56, Folder 2146)
  - Richards, Alfred Ernest (Box 56, Folder 2146)
  - Richards, Charles Brinkeroff (Box 56, Folder 2146)
  - Richards, Channing (Box 56, Folder 2147)
  - Richards, Edward L. (Box 56, Folder 2147)
  - Richards, E. L. (Eugene L.) (Box 57, Folder 2148-49)
  - Richards, George (Box 57, Folder 2150)
  - Richards, Henry B. (Box 57, Folder 2150)
  - Richards, John F. (Box 57, Folder 2150)
  - Richards, Lewis Condiot (Box 57, Folder 2151)
  - Richards, Phillip Hand (Box 57, Folder 2151)
  - Richards, William Rogers (Box 57, Folder 2152)
  - Richardson, Henry B. (Box 57, Folder 2153)
  - Richardson, Nathaniel Smith (Box 57, Folder 2153)
  - Richardson, Ralph (Box 57, Folder 2154)
  - Richardson, Roland George Dwight (Box 57, Folder 2154)
  - Richardson, Rufus Byam (Box 57, Folder 2154)
  - Richmond, George (Box 57, Folder 2155)
  - Richmond, Peter (Box 57, Folder 2155)
  - Ricker, Edward Payson (Box 57, Folder 2156)
  - Rickly, Ralph Reamer (Box 57, Folder 2156)
  - Rider, Ted (Box 57, Folder 2156)
  - Riddell, J. F., Jr. (Box 57, Folder 2157)
  - Ridgeway (Box 57, Folder 2158)
  - Riggs, Thomas L. (Father T. L. Riggs) (Box 57, Folder 2158)
  - Riley, Isaac (Box 57, Folder 2159)
  - Riley, James Whitcomb (Box 57, Folder 2159)
  - Rinke, Herman (Box 57, Folder 2160)
  - Ripley, Alfred Lawrence (Box 57, Folder 2160)
  - Ripley, George Burbank (Box 57, Folder 2161)
  - Ripley, George C. (Box 57, Folder 2161)
  - Risteen, Allan Douglas (Box 57, Folder 2161)
  - Robb, [?] (Box 57, Folder 2162)
  - Robbins, Ammi R. (Box 57, Folder 2162)
  - Robbins, Chandler (Box 57, Folder 2162)
  - Robbins, Clarence (Box 57, Folder 2163)
  - Robbins, Edward Denmore (Box 57, Folder 2163)
  - Robbins, Howard Chandler (Box 57, Folder 2163)
  - Robbins, [?] (Box 57, Folder 2163)
  - Robbins, Marcus (Box 57, Folder 2164)
  - Robbins, Milton Holley (Box 57, Folder 2164)
  - Robbins, Thomas Hamlin (Box 57, Folder 2164)
  - Robert, John S. (Box 57, Folder 2165)
  - Roberts, Edward Barry (Box 57, Folder 2165)
  - Roberts, Edwin J. (Box 57, Folder 2165)
  - Roberts, Ellis Henry (Box 57, Folder 2166)
  - Roberts, Harley Fish (Box 57, Folder 2166)
  - Roberts, Harris S. (Box 57, Folder 2166)
  - Roberts, Henry (Governor of Ct. 1905 1907) (Box 57, Folder 2167)
  - Roberts, James H. (Box 57, Folder 2168)
  - Roberts, Kenneth B. (Box 57, Folder 2168)
  - Roberts, Owen (Box 57, Folder 2169)
  - Roberts, William Jay (Box 57, Folder 2169)
  - Robertson, Abram H. (Box 57, Folder 2170)
  - Robertson, Alex G. M. (Box 57, Folder 2170)
  - Robertson, Arthur Clendenin (Box 57, Folder 2170)
  - Robertson, Gordon Marion (Pat) (Box 57, Folder 2170)
  - Robie, Burton A. (Box 57, Folder 2171)
  - Robinson, C. L. F. (Box 57, Folder 2172)
  - Robinson, Charles (Box 57, Folder 2172)
  - Robinson, Charles Leonard Frost (Box 57, Folder 2172)
  - Robinson, Clair N. (Box 57, Folder 2173)
  - Robinson, Edward S. (Box 57, Folder 2173)
  - Robinson, George Chester (Box 57, Folder 2173)
  - Robinson, Henry C. (Box 57, Folder 2174)
  - Robinson, Henry Holdship (Box 57, Folder 2174)
  - Robinson, Henry Hollister (Box 57, Folder 2174)
  - Robinson, Henry Pynchon (Box 57, Folder 2175)
  - Robinson, James H. (Box 57, Folder 2175)
  - Robinson, James J. (Box 57, Folder 2175)
  - Robinson, John Adams (Box 57, Folder 2176)
  - Robinson, Maurice H. (Box 57, Folder 2176)
  - Robinson, Samuel Curtis (Box 57, Folder 2176)
  - Robinson, William Callyhan (Box 57, Folder 2177)
  - Rockefeller, J. D. (Box 57, Folder 2178)
  - Rockefeller, James Stillman (Box 57, Folder 2179)
  - Rockwell, Alfred Perkins (Box 57, Folder 2179)
  - Rockwell, Julius (Box 57, Folder 2179)
  - Rockwell, William (Box 57, Folder 2180)
  - Rodell, Fred (Box 57, Folder 2180)
  - Rodger, James George (Box 57, Folder 2180)
  - Rodman, Thomas Clifford (Box 57, Folder 2181)
  - Rodman, William (Box 57, Folder 2181)
  - Roe, Joseph Wickham (Box 57, Folder 2182)
  - Roe, Stephen Bogert (Box 57, Folder 2182)
  - Rogers, George Hills (Box 58, Folder 2183)
  - Rogers, Henry Treat (Box 58, Folder 2183)
  - Rogers, Henry Wade (Box 58, Folder 2183)
  - Rogers, James Gamble (Box 58, Folder 2184)
  - Rogers, James Grafton (Box 58, Folder 2184)
  - Rogers, Dr. Orville F. (Box 58, Folder 2184)
  - Rogers, Rutherford D. (Box 58, Folder 2185)
  - Rogers, Samuel Towner (Box 58, Folder 2185)
  - Rogers, William Arthur (Box 58, Folder 2185)
  - Rogoff, Gordon (Box 58, Folder 2186)
  - Rollins, George William (Box 58, Folder 2186)
  - Romberg, George (Box 58, Folder 2186)
  - Roome, R. (Box 58, Folder 2187)
  - Rooney, Francis (Box 58, Folder 2187)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 58, Folder 2187)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Box 58, Folder 2188)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 58, Folder 2189)
  - Root, Alexander Porter (Box 58, Folder 2190)
  - Root, Reginald Dean (Box 58, Folder 2190)
  - Rose, R. Sheldon (Box 58, Folder 2191)
  - Roseboom, Jacob Livingston (Box 58, Folder 2191)
  - Rosen, Harold F. (Box 58, Folder 2192)
  - Rosenbloom, Arthur M. (Box 58, Folder 2192)
  - Rosenfeld, Paul L. (Box 58, Folder 2192)
  - Rosenthal, Isaac M. (Box 58, Folder 2193)
  - Ross, Charles N. (Box 58, Folder 2193)
  - Ross, Donald P. (Box 58, Folder 2193)
  - Ross, Lancelot Patrick (Box 58, Folder 2194)
  - Ross, Malcolm Harrison (Box 58, Folder 2194)
  - Ross, William Baldwin (Box 58, Folder 2194)
  - Rossiter (Box 58, Folder 2195)
  - Rostovtzeff, Michael I. (Box 58, Folder 2195)
  - Rostow, Eugene Victor (Box 58, Folder 2196-97)
  - Roth, Filbert (Box 58, Folder 2198)
  - Roth, William F., Jr. (Box 58, Folder 2198)
  - Rothery, Julian E. (Box 58, Folder 2198)
  - Rothrock, Joseph (Box 58, Folder 2198)
  - Rotival, Maurice E. H. (Box 58, Folder 2198)
  - Rowe, Alfred Hughes (Box 58, Folder 2199)
  - Rowe, Charles H. (Box 58, Folder 2199)
  - Rowe, David N. (Box 58, Folder 2199)
  - Rowe, Stanley M. (Box 58, Folder 2200)
  - Rowell, D. S. (Box 58, Folder 2200)
  - Rowell, Henry T. (Box 58, Folder 2200)
  - Rowland, David Sherman (Box 58, Folder 2201)
  - Rowland, Henry C. (Box 58, Folder 2201)
  - Rowland, Maurice T. (Box 58, Folder 2202)
  - Rowland, William Frederick (Box 58, Folder 2202)
  - Rowland, William Leonard (Box 58, Folder 2202)
  - Rowley, Henry (Box 58, Folder 2203)
  - Rowley, Rebecca M. (Box 58, Folder 2203)
  - Roy, Andrew T. (Box 58, Folder 2204)
  - Royer, Henry (Box 58, Folder 2204)
  - Ruebush, Trenton K. (Box 58, Folder 2204)
  - Ruff, William (Box 58, Folder 2205)
  - Rudge, Edwin G. (Box 58, Folder 2205)
  - Ruggles, Nancy (Box 58, Folder 2205)
  - Ruggles, Samuel (Box 58, Folder 2206)
  - Ruggles, Samuel Buckley (Box 58, Folder 2207)
  - Ruggles, Thomas Edwin (Box 58, Folder 2207)
  - Runge, Julius Herman (Box 58, Folder 2208)
  - Runk, Charles M. (Box 58, Folder 2208)
  - Rush, Charles E. (Box 58, Folder 2209)
  - Russ, Charles Trumbull (Box 58, Folder 2209)
  - Russell, Arthur, Jr. (Box 58, Folder 2209)
  - Russell, Frank Ford (Box 58, Folder 2210)
  - Russell, Dr. & Mrs. Frank (Box 58, Folder 2210)
  - Russell, Jacob Wadsworth (Box 58, Folder 2210)
  - Russell, John Edward (Box 58, Folder 2211)
  - Russell, Joseph (Box 58, Folder 2211)
  - Russell, Julius William (Box 58, Folder 2212)
  - Russell, Philip Gray (Box 58, Folder 2212)
  - Russell, Samuel Lyon (Box 58, Folder 2212)
  - Russell, William Huntington (Box 58, Folder 2213)
  - Rust, Alfred Loring (Box 58, Folder 2213)
  - Rustin, Frederick (Box 58, Folder 2214)
  - Ruth, Babe (George Herman) (Box 58, Folder 2215)
  - Ruthren, James Alexander (Box 58, Folder 2215)
  - Ryder, Ely Morgan Talcott (Box 58, Folder 2215)
  - Russell, Philip Gray (Box 58, Folder 2216)
  - Ryder, J. B. (Box 58, Folder 2216)
  - Saarinen, Eero (Box 58, Folder 2217)
  - Sachs, Arthur L. (Box 58, Folder 2218)
  - Sachs, Joseph Isidore (Box 58, Folder 2218)
  - Sadler, Holmes E. (YC 1873) (Box 58, Folder 2218)
  - Safford, George Blagdon (Box 58, Folder 2219)
  - Safford, Theodore Lee (Box 58, Folder 2219)
  - Sage, Carlton M. (Box 58, Folder 2219)
  - Sage, Dean (Box 58, Folder 2220)
  - Sage, Donald H. (Box 58, Folder 2220)
  - Sage, Leveritt Hyslip (Box 58, Folder 2220)
  - Sage, William Henry (Box 58, Folder 2220)
  - St. Hill, Thomas Nast (Box 58, Folder 2221)
  - St. John, Samuel (Box 58, Folder 2221)
  - Sajor, Valentin (Box 58, Folder 2222)
  - Saldibar, Peter S. (Box 58, Folder 2222)
  - Saliers, Earl A. (Box 58, Folder 2222)
  - Salisbury, Edward E. (Box 58, Folder 2223)
  - Salter, Charles (Box 58, Folder 2224)
  - Saltonstall, Gurdon (Box 58, Folder 2225)
  - Sanders, Frank K. (Box 58, Folder 2225)
  - Sanderson, George Augustus (Box 58, Folder 2226)
  - Sanderson, Robert L. (Box 58, Folder 2226)
  - Sane, George B. (Box 58, Folder 2227)
  - Sanford, Charles Palmer (Box 58, Folder 2227)
  - Sanford, Edward Isaac (Box 58, Folder 2228)
  - Sanford, George B. (Box 58, Folder 2228)
  - Sanford, Henry Seymour (Box 58, Folder 2229)
  - Sanford, John (Box 58, Folder 2229)
  - Sanford, Leonard Jacob (Box 59, Folder 2230)
  - Sanford, William Henry (Box 59, Folder 2231)
  - Sanger, Eugene Boutelle (Box 59, Folder 2231)
  - Sargent, Edward Rupert (Box 59, Folder 2232)
  - Sargent, G. L. (Box 59, Folder 2232)
  - Sargent, Henry Bradford (Box 59, Folder 2233)
  - Sargent, John Singer (Box 59, Folder 2233)
  - Sargent, Thomas D. (Box 59, Folder 2233)
  - Sargent, William F. (Box 59, Folder 2234)
  - Saunders, Arnold Converse (Box 59, Folder 2234)
  - Saunders, Erastus H. (Box 59, Folder 2234)
  - Savage, Albert W. (Box 59, Folder 2235)
  - Savage, Edgar Camp (Box 59, Folder 2235)
  - Savage, George Slocum Folger (Box 59, Folder 2236)
  - Savary, William Henry (Box 59, Folder 2237)
  - Sawyer, Charles H. (Box 59, Folder 2237)
  - Sawyer, Edward (Box 59, Folder 2237)
  - Sawyer, Frank A. (Box 59, Folder 2237)
  - Sawyer, George Pliny (Box 59, Folder 2238)
  - Sawyer, Herbert A. (Box 59, Folder 2238)
  - Sawyer, James Putnam (Box 59, Folder 2238)
  - Sawyer, William Babcock (Box 59, Folder 2239)
  - Saxon, Louis (Box 59, Folder 2239)
  - Saxon, O. Glenn (Box 59, Folder 2239)
  - Scaife, William Lucius (Box 59, Folder 2240)
  - Scannell, Thomas Francis (Box 59, Folder 2241)
  - Schaff, David Schley (Box 59, Folder 2241)
  - Scharmann, August C. (Box 59, Folder 2242)
  - Scharps, Benjamin (Box 59, Folder 2242)
  - Schear, Lloyd B. (Box 59, Folder 2242)
  - Schlesinger, Dr. Frank (Box 59, Folder 2243)
  - Schley, Reeve (Box 59, Folder 2243)
  - Schmalz, Arthur (Box 59, Folder 2243)
  - Schmalz, Richard A. (Box 59, Folder 2244)
  - Schmidt, Benno (Box 59, Folder 2244)
  - Schmidt, Hans (Box 59, Folder 2244)
  - Schmitz, Henry (Box 59, Folder 2244)
  - Schmucker, Francis Ritter (Box 59, Folder 2245)
  - Schollander, Donald (Box 59, Folder 2246)
  - Scholle, Frederick (Box 59, Folder 2247)
  - Scholtz, David (Box 59, Folder 2247)
  - Schoonmaker, Marius (Box 59, Folder 2247)
  - Schorer, Donald Parker (Box 59, Folder 2248)
  - Schrade, Dr. Leo (Box 59, Folder 2248)
  - Schrader, George A. (Box 59, Folder 2249)
  - Schram, Louis B. (Box 59, Folder 2249)
  - Schreiber, Carl F. (Box 59, Folder 2249)
  - Schreiber, George Gebner (Box 59, Folder 2250)
  - Schreiber, L. (Box 59, Folder 2250)
  - Schroeder, John C. (Box 59, Folder 2251)
  - Schuchert, Charles (Box 59, Folder 2251)
  - Schultz, William Eben (Box 59, Folder 2252)
  - Schumpeter, Prof. (Box 59, Folder 2252)
  - Schuneman, Carl Trueworthy (Box 59, Folder 2252)
  - Schurig, Ernest George (Box 59, Folder 2253)
  - Schwartz, J. (Box 59, Folder 2253)
  - Schwarz, G. Frederick (Box 59, Folder 2253)
  - Scott, Basil J. (Box 59, Folder 2253)
  - Scott, Charles Felton (Box 59, Folder 2254)
  - Scott, Eren Greenough (Box 59, Folder 2255)
  - Scott, Henry C. (Box 59, Folder 2255)
  - Scott, Henry W. (Box 59, Folder 2256)
  - Scott, James F. (Box 59, Folder 2256)
  - Scott, John Morin (Box 59, Folder 2257)
  - Scott, Samuel W. (Box 59, Folder 2257)
  - Scott, Walter (Box 59, Folder 2257)
  - Scoville, Alfred H. (Box 59, Folder 2258)
  - Scoville, Samuel (Box 59, Folder 2258)
  - Scoville, William H. (Box 59, Folder 2258)
  - Scripture, Edward Wheeler (Box 59, Folder 2259)
  - Scudder, Charles Locke (Box 59, Folder 2259)
  - Scully, Vincent (Box 59, Folder 2259)
  - Seabury, Rev. Samuel (Box 59, Folder 2260)
  - Seabury, Warren Bartlett (Box 59, Folder 2261)
  - Seagrave, Francis Eugene (Box 59, Folder 2261)
  - Searle, Daniel Crow (Box 59, Folder 2262)
  - Searls, Charles E. (Box 59, Folder 2262)
  - Searles, Ennie Newton (Box 59, Folder 2262)
  - Sears, Dr. Paul B. (Box 59, Folder 2263)
  - Seaver, Jay W. (Box 59, Folder 2263)
  - Seaver, William B. (Box 59, Folder 2264)
  - Sedgewick, Hubert Merrill (Box 59, Folder 2265)
  - Sedgwick, Theodore (Y. 1765) (Box 59, Folder 2266)
  - Sedgwick, Theodore (Y. 1798) (Box 59, Folder 2266)
  - Seeberger, Charles David (Box 59, Folder 2266)
  - Seed, Allen H., Jr. (Box 59, Folder 2267)
  - Seeley, Charles Scott (Box 59, Folder 2267)
  - Seeley, Lawrence F. (Box 59, Folder 2267)
  - Seely, J. F. (Y. 1860) (Box 60, Folder 2268)
  - Selly, William W. (Box 60, Folder 2269)
  - Seelye, Benjamin Berry (Box 60, Folder 2269)
  - Seidman, Saul (Box 60, Folder 2270)
  - Seifert, H. R. (Box 60, Folder 2270)
  - Seiler, Jacob Fridley (Box 60, Folder 2270)
  - Selden, Edward David (Box 60, Folder 2271)
  - Selden, Lynde (Box 60, Folder 2271)
  - Selfridge, William W. (Box 60, Folder 2271)
  - Sell, Henry Thorne (Box 60, Folder 2272)
  - Sellers, Henry Downes (Box 60, Folder 2272)
  - Sellers, James C. (Box 60, Folder 2272)
  - Senn, Dr. Milton J. E. (Box 60, Folder 2272)
  - Serat, William S. (Box 60, Folder 2273)
  - Seropyan, Christopher Dicran (Box 60, Folder 2273)
  - Setalvad, M. C. (Box 60, Folder 2274)
  - Setchell, William A. (Box 60, Folder 2274)
  - Sewall, Richard B. (Box 60, Folder 2275)
  - Sewall, Samuel (Box 60, Folder 2275)
  - Seward, George Harvey (Box 60, Folder 2275)
  - Sexton, William C. (Box 60, Folder 2275)
  - Seymour, Charles (Box 60, Folder 2276-80)
    - Photos and Negatives (Box 60, Folder 2276-80)
    - Photos of Inauguration (Box 60, Folder 2281-82)
    - Commencement Photos (Box 60, Folder 2283)
    - Receiving honorary degress from Harvard and Cambridge (Box 60, Folder 2284)
    - Photos with other presidents (Box 60, Folder 2285)
    - Visiting other schools= ceremonies (Box 60, Folder 2286)
    - In group photos (Box 60, Folder 2287-2289)
    - Snapshots and informal photos (Box 60, Folder 2290-2294)
    - Related photos (Box 60, Folder 2295)
  - Seymour, Clarence W. (Box 61, Folder 2296)
  - Seymour, David Lowry (Box 61, Folder 2296)
  - Seymour, Edward (Box 61, Folder 2297)
  - Seymour, Edward Woodruff (Box 61, Folder 2297)
  - Seymour, George Dudley (Box 61, Folder 2298)
  - Seymour, Hovey (Box 61, Folder 2299)
  - Seymour, Isaac Gurdon (Box 61, Folder 2299)
  - Seymour, John Sammis (Box 61, Folder 2299)
  - Seymour, Nathan Perkins (Box 61, Folder 2300)
  - Seymour, Storrs Ozias (Box 61, Folder 2300)
  - Seymour, Thomas Day (Box 61, Folder 2301)
  - Seymour, Thomas Y.,[?] (Box 61, Folder 2302)
  - Seymour, William Wotkyas (Box 61, Folder 2303)
  - Shaffer, Lewis William (Box 61, Folder 2304)
  - Shafner, Harris (Box 61, Folder 2304)
  - Shackleton, [?] (Box 61, Folder 2304)
  - Shaler, Nathaniel (Box 61, Folder 2304)
  - Sharp, Robert W. (Box 61, Folder 2305)
  - Sharpe, Albert H. (Box 61, Folder 2305)
  - Shaw, Edward (Box 61, Folder 2305)
  - Shaw, George Winters (Box 61, Folder 2306)
  - Shaw, Henry P. (Box 61, Folder 2306)
  - Shaw, Howard van Doren (Box 61, Folder 2306)
  - Shaw, John E. (YC 1873) (Box 61, Folder 2306)
  - Shearer, Albert B. (Box 61, Folder 2307)
  - Shearer, Sextus, Jr. (Box 61, Folder 2307)
  - Shearman, Thomas G. (Box 61, Folder 2308)
  - Shedden, William Martindale (Box 61, Folder 2308)
  - Sheen, Bishop Fulton J. (Box 61, Folder 2308)
  - Sheffield, George St. J. (Box 61, Folder 2308)
  - Sheffield, James Rockwell (Box 61, Folder 2309)
  - Sheffield, Joseph E. (Box 61, Folder 2310)
  - Sheffield, Paul King (Box 61, Folder 2311)
  - Shelden, Henry Dusenbury (Box 61, Folder 2311)
  - Sheldon, Charles A. (Box 61, Folder 2311)
  - Sheldon, Charles S. (Box 61, Folder 2312)
  - Sheldon, Edward P. (Box 61, Folder 2312)
  - Sheldon, Joseph (Box 61, Folder 2312)
  - Sheldon, Winthrop Dudley (Box 61, Folder 2313)
  - Shelton, William R. (Box 61, Folder 2313)
  - Shelton, Henry Tweedy (Box 61, Folder 2313)
  - Shepard, Charles Upham (Box 61, Folder 2314)
  - Shepard, Charles Upham, Jr. (Box 61, Folder 2314)
  - Shepard, Henry Hudson (Box 61, Folder 2315)
  - Shepard, Merrill (Box 61, Folder 2315)
  - Shepard, Oscar C. (Box 61, Folder 2315)
  - Shepard, Thomas H. (Box 61, Folder 2316)
  - Shepard William (Box 61, Folder 2316)
  - Shepatin, Nathan (Box 61, Folder 2317)
  - Sheppard, [Eustace] Morrow (Box 61, Folder 2317)
  - Sheppard, [John] Morris (Box 61, Folder 2317)
  - Sheppard, Thomas Trovillo (Box 61, Folder 2318)
  - Sheppard, Walter Bradley (Box 61, Folder 2318)
  - Sherburn (Box 61, Folder 2318)
  - Sherer, A. W. (Box 61, Folder 2318)
  - Sherman, Alton L. (Box 61, Folder 2319)
  - Sherman, Charles Phineas (Box 61, Folder 2319)
  - Sherman, Charles Selden (Box 61, Folder 2319)
  - Sherman, Darwin W. (Box 61, Folder 2319)
  - Sherman, Edward Augustine (Box 61, Folder 2320)
  - Sherman, Frederick, Deming (Box 61, Folder 2320)
  - Sherman, Lucius Adelno (Box 61, Folder 2320)
  - Sherman, Roger (Box 61, Folder 2321)
  - Sherman, Roger Minott (Box 61, Folder 2322)
  - Sherrill, Charles Hitchcock (Box 61, Folder 2322)
  - Shevlin, Edward Leonard (Box 61, Folder 2323)
  - Shevlin, Mrs. Thomas L. (Box 61, Folder 2323)
  - Shew, William (Box 61, Folder 2324)
  - Shiff, Philip R. (Box 61, Folder 2324)
  - Shipley, Joseph Lucian (Box 61, Folder 2324)
  - Shipman, Arthur Leffingwell (Box 61, Folder 2325)
  - Shipman, Frank Robinson (Box 62, Folder 2326)
  - Shipman, Nathanial (Box 62, Folder 2326)
  - Shiras, George (Box 62, Folder 2327)
  - Shirley, Arthur (Box 62, Folder 2327)
  - Shiverick, Andrew F. (Box 62, Folder 2328)
  - Shoemaker, Mrs. Curtis (Box 62, Folder 2328)
  - Shoemaker, Lazarus Denison (Box 62, Folder 2328)
  - Shorter, Frederick N. (Box 62, Folder 2329)
  - Shorter, Frank (Box 62, Folder 2329)
  - Show, Stewart Bevier (Box 62, Folder 2329)
  - Showalter, John William (Box 62, Folder 2330)
  - Shulman, Harry (Box 62, Folder 2330)
  - Siang, Cheug Cheu tuug (Box 62, Folder 2330)
  - Sibley, Josiah Y. (Box 62, Folder 2331)
  - Siccama, Tom (Box 62, Folder 2331)
  - Sidenberg, George Monroe (Box 62, Folder 2331)
  - Sigerist, Dr. Henry E. (Box 62, Folder 2331)
  - Silcox, F. A. (Box 62, Folder 2332)
  - Silk, Edmund Taite (Box 62, Folder 2332)
  - Sill, Edward Rowland (Box 62, Folder 2332)
  - Sill, George Griswold (Box 62, Folder 2333)
  - Silliman, Augustus Ely (Box 62, Folder 2333)
  - Silliman, Benjamin, Sr. (Box 62, Folder 2333)
  - Silliman, Benjamin, Jr. (Box 62, Folder 2334)
  - Silliman, Benjamin III (Box 62, Folder 2334)
  - Simmons, Edward Helfenstein (Box 62, Folder 2334)
  - Simmonds, Ralph Merriam (Box 62, Folder 2335)
  - Simmons, Fred (Box 62, Folder 2335)
  - Simpson, F. Bradford (Box 62, Folder 2335)
  - Simpson, Hartley (Box 62, Folder 2335)
  - Simpson, Miriam (Box 62, Folder 2335)
  - Simpson, Thomas Augustus (Box 62, Folder 2335)
  - Sims, Robert Gill (Box 62, Folder 2336)
  - Sims, William E. (Box 62, Folder 2336)
  - Sims, William Sowden (Box 62, Folder 2336)
  - Sinnot, Ednund Wake (Box 62, Folder 2337)
  - Sizer, Theodore (Box 62, Folder 2338)
  - Skiff, Norton Myron (Box 62, Folder 2339)
  - Skillman, John (Box 62, Folder 2339)
  - Skinner, Aaron Nichols (Box 62, Folder 2339)
  - Skinner, J. J. (Box 62, Folder 2340)
  - Skinner, Richard (Box 62, Folder 2341)
  - Skinner, Samuel W. (Box 62, Folder 2341)
  - Sklar, George (Box 62, Folder 2341)
  - Slack, Henry Richmond (Box 62, Folder 2342)
  - Slaughter, Mr. & Mrs. John Bunyan (Box 62, Folder 2342)
  - Slay, William Merrick (Box 62, Folder 2342)
  - Sleight, Brinley Dering (Box 62, Folder 2343)
  - Slemmons, J. Morris (Box 62, Folder 2343)
  - Slidell, Thomas (Box 62, Folder 2343)
  - Slifer, Ernest Wilbur (Box 62, Folder 2344)
  - Sloane, William (Box 62, Folder 2344)
  - Smalley, George Washborn (Box 62, Folder 2344)
  - Smalley, John (Box 62, Folder 2344)
  - Smith, Allen (Box 62, Folder 2345)
  - Smith, Arthur N. (Box 62, Folder 2345)
  - Smith, Azariah (Box 62, Folder 2345)
  - Smith, Benjamin (Box 62, Folder 2345)
  - Smith, Boyd Milford (Box 62, Folder 2345)
  - Smith, C. M. (Box 62, Folder 2345)
  - Smith, Chard P. (Box 62, Folder 2345)
  - Smith, Charles (Box 62, Folder 2346)
  - Smith, Charles Edwin (Box 62, Folder 2346)
  - Smith, Charles Henry (Box 62, Folder 2347)
  - Smith, Charles Robert (Box 62, Folder 2348)
  - Smith, Charles Robinson (Box 62, Folder 2348)
  - Smith, Charles S. (Box 62, Folder 2348)
  - Smith, Charles Waterman (Box 62, Folder 2349)
  - Smith, Clinton G. (Box 62, Folder 2349)